孩子们 你这辈子有时会看到某个人
Kids, sometimes in life you see someone
让你顿时就感受到
and you just instantly know
这就是你要找的那个人
this is the person for you.
这种事随时都会发生
It can happen anywhere.
即便是在洗纹身诊所的等候室里
Even the waiting room\nof a tattoo removal clinic.
比如我就遇到了...
And that's what happened when I met...
Stella\n...Stella.
喔 股沟蝴蝶纹身
Ah, the butterfly tramp stamp.
我就是靠这个谋生的
My bread and butter.
我想这背后一定有个分手不快乐\n借酒浇愁的故事吧
So I'm guessing that the real storyinvolves a bad breakup and some booze.
除非这是帮派纹身
Unless it's a gang tattoo,
那样的话 要想找个新老大投靠需要花些时间了
in which case, I think it's\ntime to find a new gang.
不是的 我一开始是想纹一只毛毛虫\n可几周之后 突然之间...
No, I just thought it would be cool to get a caterpillar\ntattoo,and then a few weeks went by,\nand all of a sudden...
好了 10个治疗期 每次一个小时 就能除掉了
Well, I can get rid of it\nin ten one-hour sessions,
但我得提前告诉你 激光手术是很疼的
but, I should warn you,\nlaser surgery's very painful.
是啊 我想你会发现我对忍耐疼痛是很有一手的
Well, I think you'll find I have a very high\ntolerance for pain.
就在昨晚 我看了有史以来最烂一部电影
Just last night, I sat through\nthe worst movie ever made.
噢 《号太空密令》?\n(该片被评为史上最烂电影)
Oh, Plan 9 From Outer Space?
不 最糟的一部电影 《命运之手马诺斯》
No, the worst movie--\nManos: Hands of Fate.
噢 我是个医生 上的医学院
Uh, I'm a doctor,\nwent to medical school.
就是《9号太空密令》如果你不信的话\nPamela剧院正在演
It's Plan 9.\nIf you don't believe me,it's playing down\nat the Pamela Theater.
我还就不信了 医生
Uh-huh.\nI don't believe you, Doctor.
那你今晚有什么安排?
Well, what are you\ndoing tonight?
好啊
Hello.
- 嘿 Ted\n- 嘿
Hey, Ted.\nHey.
嘿 快收起来 今晚我请
Hey, put that away.\nTonight's on me.
噢 不 不行 不好啦
Oh, no, no, don't...
来吧 我坚持
Come on, I insist.
你人真好 谢谢了
That's so nice. Thank you.
嘿 伙计们 这是我朋友Ted
Hey, guys,\nthis is my friend Ted.
他要请客
He wants to pay.
- 喔 哇 好啊 谢谢了
- 1 2 3 4\nOh, wow. Oh, yay.\nWow, thank you.One, two, three, four.
有什么问题吗
Is something wrong?
没有 我只是...
No, it's just, um...
我只是觉得有些尴尬 我原本以为是和她约会来着
I'm just a little embarrassed.I thought this was a date.
不过没什么啦 放心吧
But it's no big deal.Don't worry about it.
怎么了
What's wrong?
Ted很不好意思 他以为是要约会
Ted's embarrassed-- he\nthought this was a date.
Ted以为这是约会
Ted thought this was a date.
Stella 你知道Ted以为这是约会吗
Stella, did you know Ted\nthought this was a date?
什么? 我不能和病人约会的 这是AMA的规定\n(美国医学学会)
What? I'm not allowed\nto date a patient.It's an AMA rule.
她不能和病人约会 这是AMA的规定
She's not allowed to date patients.It's an AMA rule.
- 她不能和病人约会 \n- 是啊 我"听说"了
She's not allowed to date...Yeah, I got it.
我们都"听说"了
MAN: We all got it.
Ted是个笨蛋
Ted's a schmuck.
第一次治疗
- 你还买了所有人的票\n- 是啊 是啊
And you bought all the tickets.\nYeah, yeah.
嘿 你是对的
Hey, you were right.
这辈子看过最烂的电影了
Worst movie-going\nexperience ever.
当然和电影本身毫无关系
Of course, it had nothing\nto do with the movie.
- 很抱歉让你误会了\n- 不 没什么啦
I am so sorry that you\nthought that was a date.No, it's fine.
我还和你们一群女生玩了一晚上呢
I got to hang out with you\non girls' night out.
好吧 如果你不能和病人约会
All right, so if you're not\nallowed to date a patient,
那我就..我就等到这10次治疗结束
I'll just... I'll wait until\nthese ten session are up
那时候我再约你出去
and then I'll ask you out then.
那我要提前知会你一声
Well, then,fair warning:
我是不会答应你的
I'm going to say no.
是吗? 我从你那里得到了复杂的讯号
Really? I'm getting mixed\nsignals from you.
感觉你好象盯着我屁股看了半天
I feel like you've been staring\nat my ass for quite some time.
- 为什么 你结婚了吗?\n- 没有
What, you're married?\nNo.
- 有男朋友?\n- 没有
Boyfriend?\nNo.
- 有女朋友?\n- 没有
Lesbian?\nNo.
- 对白人有歧视?\n- 没有
Only date black guys?\nNo.
然而你非常肯定地告诉我\n10周以后
And yet you can say\nwith absolute confidence
如果我约你出去 你的答案将会是...
that ten weeks from now,\nif I ask you out on a date,your answer will be...
不行
No.
不行....恩....
No... Hmm.
她是什么意思呢
What could she mean
说不行
when she says no?
我不知道 太晦涩难懂了
I don't know,it is totally cryptic.
一切皆有可能
This is far from over.
从现在起我们有10周的时间
We're talking ten weeks from now.
谁知道到那时她怎么想呢
Who knows what she'll want then?
我是说 你现在知道自己10周后想吃什么午餐么?
Do you know what you're going to wantfor lunch ten weeks from now?
去Sloppy Joe 吃鸡尾虾 喝奶昔
Sloppy Joe, shrimp cocktail\nand a milk shake.
Ted 你知道一个女人决定是否和这个男人上床时\n需要花多久时间吗
Ted, do you know how long\nit takes a woman to decide whether or not\nshe's going to sleep with a guy?
8.3秒
8.3 seconds.
之后她就做出了决定
After that,her decision is made.
铁了心 不会改变的
She will not change her mind.
太荒谬了
That's ridiculous.
是吗?
Is it?
描述一下你和Stella相处的前8.3秒吧
Describe your first\n8.3 seconds with Stella.
后腰部蝴蝶纹身 到你了
Lower back butterfly tattoo--you're up.
起初的见面并不顺利
So we got off to a rocky start.
对有的人来说也许前途不佳\n但我可以扭转局面的 好吗
That may be a problem for some guys,but I get better over time.\nRight?
我又不是什么流行歌曲
I'm not some Top 40 song--
那么容易被人传唱
我是很复杂的 需要时间和反复聆听
I'm complex.I require time and multiple listens.
我就是那首《阶梯》
I'm "Stairway to Heaven."
哇 Roger Daltrey在墓地里翻身了喔
Wow, Roger Daltrey just\nrolled over in his grave.
不是他唱的 是吧
That's not the right guy, is it?
他也没死 是不是?
He's not even dead, is he?
我觉得很好呢 Ted
I think that's great, Ted.
你可以完全按照自己想的去做
You can do whatever you set your mind to.
事实上 你启发了我
In fact, you've inspired me.
我再也不要咬指甲了
I'm going to stop biting my nails.
- 可是宝贝 这是你的爱好啊\n- 我知道
But, baby, you love\nbiting your nails.
但我要为了Ted这么做
I know, but I'm doing this for Ted.
天啊 太难了
God, this is really hard.
给我10次疗程的时间
Give me ten sessions,
我要让她改变答案
I'm going to turn that "no"\ninto a "yes."
是吗Ted? 你真这么想?
Really, Ted?\nMm-hmm.You think so?\nMmm.
好吧 那告诉我那次疗程后来进行得如何
Well, tell me, how did\nthe rest of that session go?
会有一点疼
This is going to hurt a little.
没关系 我忍得住
Yeah, well, I can handle pain.
有一次我去打网球...
This one time\nI was playing tennis, and...
是啊 但是洗纹身真的很疼啦
Yeah, but tattoo removal really hurts.
换作谁都会叫成那样的
Everyone probably sounds like that.
医生 你没事吧 我听到这里有女人的叫声
Doctor, are you all right?I heard a woman\nscreaming in here.
未来还有9次
Here's to nine more great sessions.
一周周这样过去了
weeks went by.
第二次疗程时 我对她讲述了\n如何与城里的孩子度过了一个夏天
The second session I told her\nabout how I spent a summer working with inner-city kids.
第三次疗程 我们只用法语聊天
The third session we both spoke\nnothing but French.
第四次疗程 我让她大笑不止\n从椅子上摔了下来
The fourth session\nI made her laugh so hardshe fell out of her chair.
所以到了第五次见面的时候
So by the time the fifth\nsession came around...
还是不行
Still no.
为什么啊 我都耍上杂技了
What's up with that?I mean, I juggled.
耍杂技? 我以为你是要打动她呢
You juggled?I thought you were\ntrying to impress her.
你还玩魔术呢
You do magic.
杂技怎么会比魔术逊色
How is juggling\nany lamer than magic?
魔术才不逊色
Magic's not lame.
我搞不懂
I don't get it.\nI mean...
这叫逊吗?
Is this lame?
Barney 别这样
(screams)\nOh, Barney, no, no.
- 我们说过不在桌子上玩火球的\n- 你搞什么啊
We said no fireballs at the table.What the hell is wrong with you?
这里到处都是酒
There's alcohol in here.
Barney...我们以前说好的
Barney...\nI...We've talked about this.
这是违反消防规定的
It's a fire code violation.
- 是的 可是Ted他刺激我\n- 不 才不是 你消停会儿吧
Yeah, but Ted provoked me.No, no, you are on a time-out.
自己坐那边去
Go sit over there.
- 可是...\n- 快去
But...\nGo!
总之呢 我就是不明白
Anyway... I don't get it.
她现在也该对我动心了啊
She should be into me by now.
你能行的 Ted 我说过我不会再咬指甲了
You know, you can do this, Ted.I said that I would\nstop biting my nails,
哒哒拉哒
and kablam-ey.
把它当作是个挑战
It's just a challenge.
你光着屁股在人家面前时\n要想打动对方 没那么容易的
It can't be easy to woo someonewhile you're sticking your\nnaked butt in their face.
狒狒就不是
Works for baboons.
那是种"表示"
It's called "presenting."
我还有四次治疗 一定有什么地方是被我忽略的
I got four sessions left.Ther-There's got to be\nan angle I'm not seeing.
你不会改变她的想法的 Ted 死了心吧
You can't turn a "no"\ninto a "yes," Ted.Can't be done.
我说不好 Barney
I don't know, Barney.
有时坚持不懈是会有回报的 最终我不就答应了么
I mean, sometimes\npersistence pays off.I said "yes" eventually.
不 你才没有
No, you didn't.
你说"不行 我们是朋友"
You were like, "No, we\ncan't, we're friends.
- "如果我们打乱组织的氛围"\n- 是跟Ted说
It would mess up the\ndynamic of the group."To Ted.
噢 对
Oh, right.
等一下
Wait a second.
等一下 我想到了
Wait a second,\nI got the angle.
先生 请不要吼我
Sir, please don't yell at me,
因为人们对我吼 我很容易就会哭
because when people yell at me,I have a tendency to start crying.
请不要这样
Please don't do it.
Abby 我告诉过你的 他们要是不礼貌\n就挂了电话
Abby, I've told you before.\nPlease.When they're rude to you,\nhang up the phone.
快啊 你可以的 挂上电话
...how difficult it\nis for me to... Go on,you can do this, hang up.
Abby 挂了
Abby,hang it up.
我很忙 没空浪费时间
I am too busy\nto waste my time...
真对不起 我只是希望病人能够对你友好些
I'm sorry, I just wishthat some of the patients\nwould be nicer to you.
接待小姐
The receptionist.
就是我的切入点了
That's my way in.
我喜欢 勾引接待小姐
I like this.Seduce the receptionist.
- 真是个好主意\n- 不是的
That's a great plan.That's not the plan.
那对我和Stella有什么帮助呢?
And how would that help me\nwith Stella?
谁?
Who?
计划是这样的
Here's the plan.
第六次疗程
嗨 给
Hi. Here.
我去...
I stopped--
嗨 我去买咖啡 顺便给你买了些东西
Hi, I stopped for coffeeand I... and I thought\nI'd grab you something.
喔 谢谢 你人真好
Oh, wow, thank you, that's so nice.
你就像个骑士 我该叫你Ted阁下
You're like a knight.I should call you Sir Ted.
什么?
What?
没 没什么啦 我真蠢
Nothing. Nothing.(laughing nervously):\nIt's really stupid.
Zinman医生 Ted来了
Um, Dr. Zinman, Ted's here.
谢谢 谢了 Abby
Thanks. Thanks, Abby.
现在我们就等着吧
And now we wait.
自然而然 到了第7个疗程\n她对我的看法有了改变
And sure enough,by session seven, she saw me\nin a whole new light.
好吧 我要打破自己的原则了
Okay, I'm about\nto break my big rule here.
打破吧
Break it.
好吧
Okay.
Abby每周三晚上 \n都和她教堂的朋友一起去打保龄球
Abby goes bowling with her church group\nevery Wednesday night...
她很想邀请你 但是又不好意思
Mm-hmm. ...and she really wanted\nto invite you, but she's too shy.
Abby是....
Abby is...?
我的接待员啊
My receptionist.
那天你买咖啡给她 让她很感动
You really made\nquite an impression on herwith the coffee the other day.
她总是不停地提到你
I mean, she has really\nnot stopped talking about you.
噢 Abby
Oh, Abby.
我还以为你说的是"Alan"
I thought you said "Alan."
可你刚还问"Abby是...?"
But you just said, "Abby is...?"
是啊
Right.
是的 我以为我说的是"Alan"
Right, I thought I said "Alan."
Alan是谁?
Who's Alan?
Abby是谁?
Who's Abby?
我的接待员
My receptionist.
完全正确
Exactly.
怎么回事啊
What is happening?
Ted\nTed.
你做自己就好了 别再耍小心机了
You just got to be\nyourself, no more gimmicks.
你说得对 不搞那些了
You're right, no more gimmicks.
再耍一次
One more gimmick.
你知道她的书架上放着什么吗
TED:\nYou know what's on her shelf?
一本励志书《我的力量》
That self-help book\nThe Power of Me.
我知道 我知道 但是我认为如果我看一下的话
(all groaning)\nI know, I know, but I thoughtif I read it,
我们也许就有新话题可以聊了
maybe we'd have\nsomething new to talk about.
那书其实很不错 激发了我记忆的力量
It's actually a great book.It taught me the power\nof complete memory.
能借我看看吗
Can I borrow your copy?
我落在某个地方了 我给忘了
I left it somewhere.I forget.
第八次疗程
嗨 Ted Mosby来见Zinman医生
Hi.Ted Mosby for Dr. Zinman.
嗨 Ted 我会告诉她的
Hi, Ted.\nI'll let her know.
用心电感应?
Telepathically?
你真搞笑
(laughing):\nThat's funny.
风趣 智慧 出众
That's funny, smart, and great.
真对不起 我迟到了
I am so sorry that I am late.
我每天就两分钟时间可以吃午饭
I have, like, two minutes\nfor lunch everyday.
- 真是变态\n- 是啊 我理解
It's crazy. Yeah, I understand.
我之前在家里翻那些旧书
I was just, uh, checking\nout the old bookshelf here.
我发现你看过《我的力量》
I see you've read The Power of Me.
- 真是有趣 \n- 什么? 噢 不是的
It's funny...What? Oh, no.
不不不不不 我永远都不会看那种破玩意儿的
No, no, no, no, no, I would\nnever read that piece of crap.
某个病人留下的
Some patient left it here.
噢 感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
再同意不过了 真是本垃圾
(chuckling):\nI couldn't agree more.That's total crap.
我看到有人在地铁上看 就想对他们喊\n"现实点吧 人们"
I see people reading that\non the subwayand I just want to shout,\n"Get a life, people!"
Ted 我找到你的书了
Ted, I found your book.
什么?
What?
你那本 《我的力量》 你可能不小心掉到垃圾桶里了
Your book The Power of Me.I think you accidentally\ndropped it in the garbage.
什么? 不 那不是我的
What? No, that's...\nthat's not mine.
- 我这辈子从没看过\n- 不对啊 你在大厅里一直看的
I've never seen that before\nin my life.No, you were reading it\nin the lobby.
- 什么 你肯定把我和别人搞错啦\n- 不是的 你看这里
Wha-- no, you have me confused\nwith someone else.No, no, look right here.
"来自Ted Mosby的私人图书馆"
"From the personal library\nof Ted Mosby."
就是你啊
That's you.
Ted 我不想这么说
Ted, I hate to say this,
但我想现在该搞定那个接待小姐了
but I think it's "nail\nthe receptionist" time.
我才不会呢
I'm not gonna nail the receptionist.
Ted 每个小男生都想通过搭上医生或是律师\n来见证自己的成长
Ted, every little boy\nwants to grow up to nail the doctor or the lawyer.
总得有人去勾搭接待员的
Somebody's gotta nail the receptionist.
不 我喜欢的是Stella
No. I like Stella.
好吧 我得阻止一你下了 Ted
Okay, I'm gonna stop you\nright there, Ted.
你那位Stella并不是十分完美
Your little Stella is not so perfect.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我去了那里 亲自查看了一下情况
I went down there and checked her out for myself.
是的
Yeah.
我在那里的时候
And while I was down there,
我发现她有个秘密
I discovered that she had a secret,
一个非常...可怕的秘密
a terrible... terrible secret.
什么  是什么啊
What?What is it?
等下 我去撒尿
Hold on, I gotta pee.
好了 我回来了
Okay, I'm back.
工作怎样
What's going on at work?
伙计 什么大秘密啊
What's the big secret?!
噢 噢 对
Oh. Oh, right.
嗨 我想见一下Zinman医生
Hi, I'd like to see Dr. Zinman, please.
好的 请问是什么事?
Sure, what's it regarding?
噢 我就是想见见她
Oh, I just want to see her.
看看她 见见她长什么样
Want to look at her,\nsee what she looks like.
我...我不明白
I-I don't understand.
抱歉 我是打电话时不小心按了2号键么
I'm sorry, did I accidentallyoprima numero dos when I called?
你会英语吗
Do you speak English?
我要见她!
I want to see her!
先生 请别对我吼
Sir, please don't yell at me
因为别人一吼我 我就想哭
because when people yell at me,I have a tendency to start crying.
- 你拿的是什么证书啊\n- 请不要 不要这样做
What are your credentials?!Please don't do that. Please.
我要知道自己在和谁讲话!
I want to know who am I speaking with!
起初她看上去还不错
BARNEY: At first she seemed
聪明 智慧 绝对不是你能搞定的
great, beautiful, smart,way out of your league.
但之后 我无意中听到了这样的话
But then, I overheard this conversation.
我祖父的名字 我是最后一个 所以...
...my grandfather's name--\nI was the last-born so...
噢 Abby 我的催眠治疗师来电话了吗
Oh, Abby, did my hypnotherapist call yet?
没有
No.
我什么时候才能治好这个Folliculaphilia啊?
When am I going to kick\nthis folliculaphilia?
Folliculaphilia?\nFolliculaphilia?
Folliculaphilia\nFolliculaphilia.
那是什么?
What is that?
Ted 你的女神
Ted, your perfect woman
只对有胡子的男人有兴趣
can only be attracted\nto men with moustaches.
这是我听过最蠢的事了
That is the stupidest thing\nI've ever heard.
才不是真的
That's not real.
你说得对 Ted 是我瞎编的
You're right, Ted.\nI'm just making that up.
我知道 因为根本没这种事
I know that you are\nbecause there's no such thing.
我就有点
I got it a little bit.
第九次疗程
嗨 Ted Mosby找Zinman医生
Hi. Uh, Ted Mosby for Dr. Zinman.
噢 嗨 Ted 胡子真帅
Oh, hi, Ted. Love the 'stache.
你就像年轻时的汤姆-塞立克\n不过比他帅上N倍
You look like a young Tom Selleck,only a million times handsomer.
Zinman医生 Magnum来见你了\n(汤姆-塞立克主演的电影)
Dr. Zinman, Magnum's here to see you.
开个玩笑
Just kidding.
白痴
Stupid.
抱歉我晚了 例行两分钟午饭
Sorry I'm late.\nTypical two-minute lunch.
我们很快就要....
So we are very close to getting...
为什么 这是为什么
Why? Just why?
你不记得了吗
Y-you don't remember?
(一年前)\n我跟你们每个人赌10块 我能让Ted留胡子
I'll bet anyone ten bucksI can get Ted to grow a moustache.
呃..好吧
Uh... okay.
你就为了10块钱 毁了我最后一次接近Stella的机会
You sabotaged my next to last\nchance with Stellafor ten dollars?
我知道 免费我也会这么做的
I know. I would've done it for free.
不过你欠我10块钱
But, no. You owe me ten bucks.
太过分了 我最后一次疗程就是下周
This is awful.\nMy-my tenth session is next week.
我会约她出去 \n而她则会说出英文中最沉闷的一个字
I'm gonna ask her out,\nand she's gonna saythe most demoralizing syllable\nin the English language--
不
no.
你知道吗 干脆忘了吧 我是不会问她了
You know what?\nJust forget it.I'm not even gonna ask her.
不 你得问她 她喜欢你 她亲口说的
No, you have to. She likes you.She said so herself.
我是说...
(clearing throat)\nI mean...
不是吧 你也去见过她了?
Oh, my God,\nyou went and saw her, too.
我向你发誓 我没有
I swear to you, I did not.
我妻子总是唠叨我干燥的手肘
My wife's always getting\non me about my dry elbows.
谈恋爱的感觉真不错
So good to be in\na relationship.
你有遇到什么人吗
Anyone special\nin your life?
或者是让你感兴趣的某个人?
Or maybe just someone\nyou're interested in?
对他有兴趣?
Interes-ted in?
我们应该检查一下这颗痣
You know, we should really\nget this mole checked out.
有点不正常
It's just a little irregular.
不正常? 噢 天啊
MARSHALL:\nIrregular? Oh, my God.
完蛋了 全都结束了
This is it. It's all over.
我有个病人在腰部纹了一个蝴蝶纹身
One of my patients has thislittle butterfly tattoo\nat the bottom of his back.
可以不要再提你其他的病人了吗
Can you stop talking about\nyour other patients?!
我都要死了 女人!
I'm dying here, woman!
好了 你瞧 即便有什么问题 也很容易就会治愈\n所以不用担心了
There you go. Look, even if it is something,it's easily treatable, so try to relax.
好的
Okay.
嘿 你之前说的那个有蝴蝶纹身的男人\n是怎么回事?
Hey, what was it you were saying beforeabout the guy with the butterfly tattoo?
噢 没...没什么啦 只是有点好感而已
Oh, that... that's nothing.It's just a little crush.
等结果出来我就会打给你的
So I will be calling\nyou with your results.
噢 好的 谢谢
Oh. Okay. Thank you.
噢 先生 你的书
Oh, sir, your book!
- 不是的\n- 是的
No.Yes.
她说有好感?
She said "crush"?
她有提到我?
And she was talking about me?
最后一次治疗 是最不痛苦的
NARRATOR:\nThat last session was the least painful of all.
我享受着那激光带来的每一下刺痛
I savored every searing blast\nof that laser.
全好了
All done.
我等待了十周的那一刻终于到了
The moment I'd waited\nten weeks for had arrived.
Stella...\nStella...
现在我不再是你的病人了
...now that I'm\nno longer your patient,
你愿意和我共进晚餐吗
would you like\nto have dinner with me?
- Ted 你真的不错\n- 噢 不是吧
Ted, you're a really nice guy...Oh, no.
认识你真的很开心
It has been so great\ngetting to know you.
- 我要去杀了Marshall\n- 这十周我过得很开心
I am gonna kill Marshall. I've had so much fun\nthese last ten weeks.
天啊 这比激光还要让人痛苦
Oh, my God, this is worse\nthan the laser.
我有个女儿
I have a daughter.
什么?
What?
她叫Lucy 8岁了
Her name's Lucy.\nShe's eight.
工作 然后和她一起 我的生活基本就是这样
Work and being with her,\nthat's pretty much my life.
我的社交活动就是每个月和姑娘们看场电影
My social calendar is movie night with the girls\nonce a month
在我找到保姆的时候 去年我曾经参加过一个派对
when I can get a sitter.I mean, I've been to one party\nin the past year--
圣派翠克节 很糟糕 我就早早离开了
St. Paddy's Day--\nit was awful, I left early.
但是 我唯一的空闲时间\n就是午饭那两分钟 所以...
But, really, my only free time is the two minutes\nI get for lunch, so...
这就是为何我拒绝约会
this is why I don't date.
Ted 我的时间给我这辈子最重要的人\n那就是Lucy
Ted, I only have time for one most important person\nin my life, and that's Lucy.
不管怎样 真的很开心
Anyway, it's been fun.
下次纹身前要三思哟
Next time, think before you ink.
但无论你什么时候醒来
But if you ever do wake up with, like,
发现脚踝上有只海豚\n打给我就是了
a dolphin tattoo on your ankle,\njust give me a call.
就是这样了
There it is--
她已经当妈了
she's a mom.
不可能了
It's just not gonna happen.
很遗憾 伙计
Sorry, dude.
吃只虾吧
Have a shrimp.
不用了
I'm good.
我想这只能怪我自己 她一开始就告诉我了
I guess I got no one but myself to blame. She told me right from the start
她不会答应的 所以自然...
she was gonna say no and sure enough...
等等
Wait a minute.
- 嗨\n- 嗨
Hi.\nHi.
你并没有拒绝我
You didn't actually say no
- 你指什么\n- 本来你该说不的
What do you mean?.All this time you were, uh,\nyou were supposed to say no,
但你没有 我查过了
but you didn't--\nI checked the transcript.
所以我想说的是
So, here's what I'm proposing.
你只有两分钟 是吧
Uh... You only have two minutes, right?
是的
Right.
好的 那你愿意...和我来个二分钟约会吗
Okay. You want to, uh...go on a a two-minute date with me?
上一次两分钟约会时 我收获了一个女儿
Last two-minute date I had gave me a daughter.
恩...好吧
Um... Okay.
好极了
Great.
....开始
And... go.
出租车!
Taxi!
- Ted 我只有两分钟时间\n- 我知道
Ted, I seriously only have two minutes...I know.
就只有120秒
That's like 120 seconds.
西22街 380
380 West 22nd, please.
速度快 我们着急
And step on it.\nWe're in a hurry.
西22街 380? 那是
380 West 22nd? That's...
- 这边坐\n- 谢谢
Right this way.(laughing):\nThank you, sir.
你知道 我一直都想来这里试试
You know, I have always\nwanted to try this place.
家常沙拉
House salad.\nOh.
大学在?
So, college?
斯坦福
Stanford.
卫斯理
Uh-huh. Wesleyan.
噢 真好 你认识 Adam Lazar吗?
Oh, good. Do you know Adam Lazar?
不认识 Scott Crable?
No. Scott Crable?\nMm-mm.
芝士h茄子
Eggplant parmesean.
- 谢谢\n- 已经切好了 真不错
Thanks.\nOh, already cut up. Nice.
现在买单好吗 我们15秒后要去看电影
Could we get\nthe check please.We're trying to make a movie\nin 15 seconds.
- 当然\n- 好的 谢谢
Of course.  Okay, great.
你打算怎样付
Uh, how do you want\nto do this?
你吃了h茄子 我只喝了水 所以...
You had the eggplant parm.I only really\nhad water so...
我开玩笑呢
I'm kidding.  Oh.
好了 我们走
Okay. Let's go.
- 出租车\n- 你紧张吗
Taxi! You nervous?
- 有点\n- 完全看不出来
A little bit. You can't tell at all.
那很好
Oh, good. Yeah.
好啊
Hello!
西22街 384
384 West 22nd.
15秒 电影已经开始了
15 seconds. The movie's started.
不会 有预告片 不怕
Nah, previews. We'll be fine.
啊 刚刚好 还没开始
Ah! Just in time.\nIt hasn't started yet.
我们要看什么
So, what are we seeing?
命运之手马诺斯
Manos: Hands of Fate.
全部吗
The whole thing?
只看最重要的部分
Only the important parts.
最烂的片子了
Worst movie ever.
是啊 我有5次都差点就走了
Yeah, I almost walked  out, like, five times.
我们还准时吧 出租车!
How we doing on time? Taxi!
我们还有点时间
We got a little time.
好的 要走走吗
Okay. Do you want to walk it?
- 何不呢\n- 好啊
Why not?Hello!
再见
Good-bye!
你女儿上几年级了
So what grade's your daughter in?
三年级
Third grade.
好时候
Ah! That's a good year.
是啊 她很可爱
Yeah, she's wonderful.
我只希望可以让她把烟戒了
I just wish that I could get her to quit\nsmoking, you know?
- 什么?\n- 开玩笑呢
What?  I'm kidding.
瞧 喝杯咖啡 吃块甜点?
Oh. Look,\ncoffee and dessert?
你知道这地方老是在变 \n原本有家非常可爱的意大利餐厅
You know, this neighborhood\njust keeps on changing.This used to be a cute,\nlittle Italian restaurant.
我知道 纽约嘛
I know. New York.
就像个活的有机体 总是在不停变换
It's a living organism,\nan ever-changing tapestry.
看看时间啊
Ooh, look at the time.
我们走
Let's go.
这芝士蛋糕真是太好吃了
Mmm, the cheesecake's amazing.
要花吗
Flowers?
我过敏
I'm allergic.
好的 瞧 我们已经彼此有所了解了
Okay. See?\nWe're getting to knock other.
Stella 我有个非常可爱的
Stella, I had a lovely--
外卖
Doggy bag?
Stella 我很开心
Stella, I had a lovely time.
我也是 Ted
Me, too, Ted.
以及约会
And... date.
没那么糟 是不是
That wasn't so bad, right?
不会冷场 不会尴尬
No lengthy, awkward silences.
不过甜点是有点太久了 所以...
Dessert ran a little long, so...
我就不得不省掉吻别的时间了
I had to cut the good-night kiss.
我想我可以迟到那么一次
I think I can be late just once.
- Ted...\nTed...Look, I I uld love\nto have a second date, I would.
- 我很愿意再次和你约会 真的
但我知道你现在真的没时间 但如果你有
But I understand that you really\ndon't have time right now,but if you ever do,
打给我好吗
will you give me a call?
- 好的\n- 好
Yes.Okay.
孩子们 就这样"不"变成了"是"
And that, kids, is how you turn a "no"into a "yes."
我的朋友都劝我 "Abby 要坚强
All my friends told me,\n"Abby, be strong.
- 他不配有第二次机会\n- 噢 不不不
He doesn't deserve\nanother chance."No, no, no.
- 但是我原谅你\n- 别别别介
But I forgive you!No, no, no, no!
他人看上去很好 可是却在玩弄我的感情
then he just kepttoying with my emotions
这个Ted听起来可真混蛋
This Ted guy sounds like a real jerk.
你知道你的问题出在哪儿吗
You know your problem?
你太讨人喜欢了
You're too sweet.
你不是来找医生看那个痣的吗
Aren't you going to see\nthe doctor about that mole?
噢 是的
Oh, yeah.
不过是个籽罢了
Turns out it's just\na Raisinet.
嘿 让我带你去家豪华餐厅
Hey, how would you likeme to take you out to a fancy restaurant
然后再去大血拼一番如何?
and then go on a shopping spree?
享受你应有的待遇
Treat you the way\nyou should be treated.
能让你忘记那个叫Ted的魔鬼吗?
Would that make you forget\nabout that Ted monster?
我妈妈说得不对 纽约还是有好男人的
My mom was wrong.There are nice guys in New York.
我们得先去我酒店的房间 我的床坏了
We just have to go\nby my hotel room first.My bed was broken.
我得确保他们修好了
I just have to make sure\nthey fixed it.
那如果修好的好 我们能在上面做爱\n然后再去逛街吗
Well, then if it's fixed,can we can have sex on it\nand then go shopping.
我喜欢你
I like you